At first it was rainy, you casually...
pulled out the umbrella slowly. What even is this feeling?
I can feel it through your grip
Your very own rhythm
If i just trust you with it
Will it go ok? this isn't a dream
The more i feel it the more it feels...
Like i'm forgetting something else
I want to feel it again, just for a second more...
I wanna be with you.
I want to say it i really want to, but I cant, that secret sign.
It's fine going bit by bit, as long as it's with you.
I just feel you.
I feel so happy yet it's so painful
it's without a doubt your fault, All your fault
Being alone, silent time, thinking about all sorts of things, i feel down
Love is a difficult thing
No matter what face you make
I want to see you all for myself
even if it's just for another day
I wanna be with you.
I just gotta, I just wanna, see you, miss you, tonight
Perhaps I'd be fine with being held, as long as it's you
I just follow you.
Your so sweet it brings me to tears
It's without a doubt
完璧に見せるより　そのままの
不器用なとこも全部　一つずつ　好きになって
世界が輝いて　こんなに優しいのは Tell me why？
I wanna be with you.
どうして　どうしても　言いたい　言えない Secret sign
少しずつだっていいよね　君となら
I just feel you.
嬉しくて　切ないのは
間違いなく　君のせい、君のせいさ。
君のせいさ。